brainhoney.com 2012-10-14

# BrainHoney | Privacy

## **Privacy Policy**  
**  
**

Agilix has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to our visitor and customer privacy. Privacy on the Agilix Web site (the "Site") is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our visitors and for our customers, we have established this policy as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. This privacy statement also explains the use of data collection practices of Agilix software. 

By using this Site, you are agreeing to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. If we revise our Privacy Policy we will post a notice of change thirty days prior to material changes. Any modifications to this statement will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes. 

**COLLECTED INFORMATION**

**Anonymous Information**  
You can visit the Site to read information about our company, products, and services without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. To improve the usefulness of our site, Agilix does track and analyze non-identifying, aggregate usage, and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers to administer our Site, to constantly improve the quality of our service and site performance. 

Information gathered will include the following, but not limited to, the activity of the user’s browser when user is viewing the site, the site path of visitors, and the time visitors come to our site. Agilix reserves the right to use this anonymous, aggregate summary information regarding its site visitors for internal purposes. Please note that this is not personal information, only general summaries of our visitors. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
When we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you, we will explicitly ask you for it. For example, if you choose to register your software, we will collect your name, address, telephone number, education institution or business name, and e-mail address. The personal information we collect from you will be used by Agilix to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized, and may also be used to request additional information on feedback that you provide about the product or service that you are using; to provide critical updates and notifications; to improve the product or service, or to tell you about new product releases.

Except as described in this statement, personal information you provide will not be transferred to third parties without your consent. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as sending and delivering purchases and other mailings, and answering customer questions about products or services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Site visitors may wish to request information about our products and services, or to download specific documents on the Site. Agilix visitors will be requested to provide information, such as, but not limited to, name, company or education institution, title, phone number, e-mail address and address. 

Agilix uses the information that we collect on the Site to contact visitors to further discuss their interest in our company, our services, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as marketing promotions, and to improve the services we provide you. The information is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data and is used to fulfill your request and is not provided to third parties for their use. Agilix uses secured server areas and advanced firewall technology to minimize the risk of individually identifiable information being compromised. Agilix also takes every effort to ensure that the information users provide is correct and current. Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Collection and Use of Information About Your Computer**  
Agilix software contains features that automatically: a) check for version of software you are running with the latest version available from Agilix for purposes of notifying you of updates, and b) collects information from your Agilix application and sends it to Agilix. This computer information is not personally identifiable. These features are turned on by default, so that we can collect enough information about how the product is working to keep your software up-to-date and improve the commercially released product. Information that is collected by or sent to Agilix may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Agilix or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities.

**COOKIES AND CLEAR GIFS**

**What Are Cookies**  
Cookies are files that Web browsers place on a visitor’s computer hard drive and are used to allow a more enjoyable visit with easier use of site and to more accurately track visitor behavior to our site. Cookies come in two flavors: session and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you’ve closed your browser or turned off your computer. Cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser, unless you choose to identify yourself voluntarily. You may choose to identify yourself for any one of the following reasons: asking the browser to remember your username and password, by responding to a promotional offer, when personalizing a Web page or requesting more information on a product or service, otherwise you remain as an anonymous Web site visitor. 

**How We Use Cookies**  
When you interact with the Site, we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. When you come to the Site, our Web server uses cookies to improve our visitors’ interaction with our site. 

Agilix uses session cookies to track Web visitor behavior and to allow our customers to immediately save the username and password as well as personal settings on specific pages. This allows Agilix to process your saved login information and quickly log you into the product. Session cookies also help us make sure you are who you say you are after you’ve logged in. 

Agilix uses persistent cookies, that only Agilix can read and use, to identify the fact that you are an Agilix customer or a prior Agilix Web site visitor (whatever the case may be). We are especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. Users who disable their Web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will still be able to browse our Web site; however, they may lose some of the functionality provided by the use of persistent cookies.  
**  
SECURITY**

Our Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Data under our control. When our Site is accessed using Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.0, or higher, or Mozilla Firefox 1.0, or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that Data is safe, secure, and available only to you. Agilix also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and hosts the product in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, Agilix provides unique usernames and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs on. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of Data. 

**THIRD PARTY SITES**

The Site contains links to other Web sites. Agilix is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites. Customers and visitors will need to check the policy statement of these other Web sites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential. 

**CONTACT US**

If users have questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, they should first contact us by e-mail at [sales@agilix.com](mailto:sales@agilix.com). You can also call us by phone at 801.932.1220
